

Eduard Eugenio Duarte-Sepulveda

Senior Solution Architect

+57 311 430 0319 · eduard.duarte@hotmail.com

Linked-in

Skills Fast Learner Adaptability Communication Skills Problem Solving Solution Design Leadership Languages Spanish; Castilian English

Profile

I am a master in software engineering with 12 years of work experience of which 5 years working as a Software Architect working with AWS Cloud technologies, and languages such as Java, Phyton, Java, NodeJs, JavaScript, TypeScript, Visual Basic, Cobol, Golang, CSS, HTML

I have extensive experience working in software in the banking sector from the analysis of applications to complex architectures with high resilience, where I have stood out as a natural leader, contributing to each of the teams and projects where I have worked.

Employment History

Solution Architect, Sophos Solutions SAS, adviser of Bancolombia bank, Medellin, Colombia

April 2020 - Present

Project: Software architecture for Bancolombia Clients

Functions: Design resilient Cloud Architectures

Technologies: AWS cloud

Software architect, Lucasian Labs SAS, adviser of Banco Caja Social, Bogota, Colombia

November 2017 — April 2020

Project: Customized Solutions Project (SAM)

Functions: Architecture Design Technologies: Oracle, Xamarin

Software architect, Vector ITC Group, adviser of Santander bank and Davivienda bank, Bogotá, Colombia

September 2015 - November 2017

Project: Condor, Premier Credit, PSE Payments

Functions: Banco de Santander Architecture Design

Technologies: Java, HTML, Angular

Programmer analyst, Proyectos Compartidos Ltda, adviser of Davivienda bank and Banco de Bogota, Bogota, Colombia February 2013 - September 2015

Project: Daviplata and Profitability of agreements

Functions: Analysis and construction of requirements

Technologies: Java, VBA and Cobol

Developer Engineer, SAIP S.A.S, adviser of Transport Ministry of Colombia, Bogota, Colombia

February 2012 - October 2012

Project: Appraisal Ministry of transport

Functions: Design and construction of mobile App

Technologies: Android, Java, Gradle, HTML

Education

Master in Software Engineering, Universidad de Los Andes, Bogota, Colombia

August 2019 - August 2021

Master in Information Technology Architectures, Universidad de Los Andes, Bogota, Colombia

August 2019 - August 2021

Electronic Engineer, Universidad Francisco de Paula Santander, Cucuta, Colombia

January 2007 - December 2011

Courses

AWS Certified, Amazon

2020

Development of applications with data management in memory - Java 2018

Development of applications with graphical interface, event management, classes and Java-objects.

2018

Variables and control structures in object-oriented programming - Java 2018

Spring-framework-5 Building real web applications with Spring Framework 5 & Spring Boot: Thymeleaf, JPA, Security, REST, Angular, WebFlux

2018

Oracle-certification-associate-no-official study of the entire structure of the Oracle Certification Associate Course for learning the content of the Oracle Certified Partner Exam.

2018

Angular: From zero to expert creating applications (Angular 6+) All angular content using TypeScript and best practices offered by the angular team.

2017

Advanced Angular: Take your bases to the next level - MEAN, Google Signin, JWT, file upload, lazyload, optimizations, Git, GitHub, admin panel

2017

Database modeling with golang & Database modeling with golang & DBMS directly from golang to postgresql

2017

Technical knowledge

Operating systems

Linux, Windows

Programming languages

Angular, Java, NodeJs, JavaScript, TypeScript, Visual Basic, Cobol, Golang, CSS, HTMI

Databases

Oracle, Postgres, DynamoDB, RedShift

Web Servers

Nginx, Apache Tomcat, Microsoft IIS, GlassFish

UML Modeling and Design

Functional Knowledge

Git, SVN, Github, Bickbuket, GitFlow

References

Laura Marcela Paez Rianos from Project Manager and Director SGC - Lucasian Labs SAS

+57 1 315 812 73 11 · <u>lpaez@lucasian.com</u>

Sonia Patricia Rodriguez Martinez from Project Manager in Vector ITC Group - Vector ITC Group

+57 1 3165241973 · sprodriguez@vectoritcgroup.com

Milton Castellanos from Project Manager - Proyectos Compartidos +57 1 316 524 72 43 · mcastellanos@mail.proyectos-compartidos.com